### Peter Sivak

email: p.sivak91@gmail.com Fairfield, CA +1-707-770-6743

https://peter-sivak.webs.com/
sivo91 (Peter) (github.com)

### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Seeking entry level position in Web development.

Hardworking, dedicated retired professional athlete with winning attitude who delivers on goals – literally -is preparing for the next chapter in life to become front end Web developer.

My goal is to remain productive member of our family and continue to achieve success in life, to become a leader and recognized expert in a field of computer science. I believe Information Technology is going to play even greater role in our life than it does now, beyond our wildest imagination.

The past twenty years had taught me how to succeed and shine in crowd, taught me resilience and discipline. I learned to fight for every moment and learn to keep winning momentum.

My past career molded my hard-working character and righteous personality. I am used to work under pressure and deliver consistent work in the least amount of time.

These attributes allowed me to achieve success and win championships and numerous personal awards. Although, my previous career is over and it soon becomes a warm but distant memory, I look forward to a bright future and challenges that a field of computer science will bring.

# **QUALIFICATIONS**

Web Interactivity
Adobe InDesign
Adobe Illustrator
Photoshop
C++ Fundamentals
HTML, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap
JavaScript
Visual Basic
Microcomputer Application
Game Coding (2d Phaser3, 3d Three.JS) \*current class
Web Development
UDEMY: John Smilga(JS), Traversy Media(JS)

#### WORK EXPERIENCES



FedEx delivery, part-time

06/12/2020 - ongoing

Daily exceeding metrics 15/ pkgs/h averaging 22 pkgs/h in the shortest time



Professional hockey player

I was forward , yet universal -playing in all situations- on the first line, first power-play unit and killing penalties and helping the defense

I was a high scorer, yet my priority was team success -I always passed the puck to teammate who had better chance to score

I worked hard- after game or practice, I still added conditioning on the ground

#### **EUROPE**

•	HK 32 Liptovsky Mikulas	Liptovsky Mikulas, Slovakia,	09/1999 - 03/2001
•	HK Dukla Trencin	Trencin, Slovakia,	09, 2001 - 04, 2007
•	MSHK Zilina	Zilina, Slovakia,	09, 2006 - 04, 2008
•	HK Zlin	Zlin, Czech Republic,	09,2008-04,2011
•	MSHK Zilina	Zilina, Slovakia,	09/2011 - 04/2012

#### **USA**

CD.	. <b>.</b>		
•	SF Bulls, ECHL	San Francisco, CA,	10/2012 - 04/2012
•	Alaska Aces, ECHL	Anchorage, AK,	10/2013 - 06/2014
•	Stockton Thunder, ECHL	Stockton, CA,	10/2014 - 01/2014
•	Orlando Solar Bears, ECHL	Orlando, FL,	02/ 2014 -04/ 2014
•	Fort Wayne Komets, ECHL	Fort Wayne, IN,	10/2015 - 12/2015
•	Alaska Aces, ECHL	Anchorage, AK,	12/2015 - 04/2016
•	Alaska Aces, ECHL	Anchorage, AK,	10/2016 - 04/2017
•	Utah Grizllies, ECHL	Salt Lake City, UT	10/2016 - 10/2016
•	Rapid City Rush, ECHL	Rapid City, SD,	10/2016 - 04/2017
•	Worchester Sharks, AHL	Worchester, MA,	03/2013 - 05/2013
•	Bridgeport Sound Tigers, AHL	Bridgeport, CT,	11/2014 - 12/2014
•	Tulsa Oilers, ECHL	Tulsa, OK,	10/2018 - 04/2019

#### **CANADA**

Abbotsford Heat, AHL Abbotsford 09/2013 - 10/2013



# Assistant coach

Recording, analyzing, highlighting individual players stats during the game, game situations, teaching on -ice, off-ice to improve strategy to win the games

Tulsa Oilers, ECHL Tulsa, OK, 10/2018 - 04/2019

# **EDUCATION**

**EUROPE:** Elementary School Slovakia, EU 09/1986-05/1994 Slovakia, EU **Business Academy** 09/1994 -05/1998

**USA:** Tulsa, OK and Napa, CA 2019 **GED** 

Full time student (Completed 41 Units, current GPA = 4.00)

Web Development Solano Community College, Fairfield, Ca 2020 - ongoingWeb Development Santa Rosa Junior College Santa Rosa, Ca 2020 – ongoing

# **LANGUAGES**

English - goodSlovak - excellent Czech -- excellent

### **AWARDS**

Slovak Extraliga National Champion	1 <sup>st</sup> Place EU	2003 - 2004
Slovak Extraliga	3 <sup>rd</sup> Place EU	2004 - 2005
Slovak Extraliga	2 <sup>nd</sup> Place EU	2006 - 2007

ECHL Kelly Cup Champion ALASKA Aces 1st Place, USA 2013 – 2014

#### Personal awards

ECHL Performer of the Year (+49)

ECHL Sportsmanship Award (10 PM)- honors the player judged "to have exhibited the best type of sportsmanship and gentlemanly conduct with a high standard of playing ability."

ECHL ALL-STAR Team 2015 - 2016

ECHL ALL-STAR Team NHL network televised game 2016 - 2017

# **LINKS**

sivo91 (Peter) (github.com)

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peter\_Siv%C3%A1k

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MYR07WEBbPg

https://www.eliteprospects.com/player/34714/peter-sivak

https://www.hockeydb.com/ihdb/stats/pdisplay.php?pid=57465

# **CURIOSITY**

The scorer of one of the fastest goals in hockey history. 4:08